NOGRADY:
Today really marks
the first stage
of an unprecedented
technological advancement.
We have begun to identify
so-called Goldilocks planets.
These are planets that share
a similar relationship
with their sun
as we have with ours.
If a planet's too
far away from its sun,
it's too cold.
If it's too close to
its sun, it's too hot.
But for an Earth-like planet,
the distance is just right.
Potentially perfect
for sustaining life.
We have finally managed
to identify one planet
that is the right distance
from its star to hold water
and is the right mass
to sustain an atmosphere.
Every 24 hours,
our station in Hawaii
will transmit
a signal to Landsat 7,
our deep orbiting satellite,
which will amplify
and relay the signal
to our targeted planet
which is, rather grandly,
entitled Planet G.
If there is intelligent life
out there, and they come here
it's going to be like
Columbus and the Indians.
Only, we're the Indians.
Ladies and gentlemen, please
prepare to bear witness
to the making of history.
Start transmission.
JACKIE: It seems as though
NASA is setting up shop
right here in
our own backyard.
Today, the Beacon
International Project
was launched.
Satellite dishes
here on Oahu
sending out very
powerful signals
into deep space
with an attempt
to communicate
with anyone...
STONE: Another round,
birthday boy.
JACKIE: ...or anything that
might be out there listening.
A toast.
Happy birthday,
little brother.
I'm wishing you
success and growth,
and happiness.
May this be
a great year for you.
It's going to
be a great year.
I love you.
I love you, too.
So, in the great
Hopper family tradition,
this year I'm quoting
from Coach John Wooden.
Johnny.
"Adversity is
the state in which man
"most easily
becomes acquainted
with himself
"being especially free
of admirers then."
Cheers.
I'm not cheers-ing that.
It's a very
good quote for you.
"I may be free of
admirers right now
but there is still time"?
Will you shut up?
Light your cupcake
and raise your glass.
Did you get me that?
Yes, I got you that.
Thank you,
that's very sweet.
You're welcome.
You're very welcome.
I got this guy, Tony.
He said he can get you
a construction job.
All you need to
do is call him.
Could I get a beer
and a chicken burrito,
please?
Sorry, kitchen's closed.
STONE: You're not going
to call him, are you?
Give Tony my best,
but I don't need you
or Tony's help,
for that matter.
You can call him or
join me in the Navy.
No.
Great. All right.
Happy birthday.
Blow out your candle
and make a wish.
Do not waste
a wish on a girl.
Wish for a job,
an apartment.
A new alternator belt,
so I don't have to
drive you everywhere.
A job, or...
You said "job" twice.
It's my birthday and my wish.
All right?
Please don't waste it.
You just wasted
that wish, didn't you?
I'm going in.
You're not going in.
How do I look?
Wait, let me
just fix that.
Awesome!
All right, princess,
go get 'em.
Great start.
Ugh.
What seems to
be the problem?
I want a chicken burrito.
Johnny, chicken burrito her.
BARTENDER: It ain't happening.
Chicken burrito her.
Kitchen's closed, Hopper.
What's your name?
I'm hungry.
That's not your name.
If you give me five minutes
I will get you
your chicken burrito.
Five minutes,
starting now.
(BELCHES)
Chicken burrito time, I'm out.
Chicken burrito,
roger that.
HOPPER: Wait! Hi!
No! Let's just...
Just one twist of the key
and we will be good.
How are you, ma'am?
How you doing?
Burritos, right there.
It's closed.
Too late, pal.
Okay.
It's right there. Please?
It's too late
to eat a burrito.
Too many complex carbs.
$3.99...
(GRUNTING) Chicken burrito.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE)
I got it!
Hey! Freeze!
(ALARM RINGING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
I got a burrito!
I got it!
Freeze!
(GASPS)
Stay down!
MAN: He's getting back up!
(GRUNTING)
STONE: I've had it!
Look at yourself!
How is it that you
screw everything up?
By the way, that girl
you were trying to
impress last night,
do you know who
her father is?
Admiral Shane!
He runs the whole damn fleet!
So, now you're messing
with my job. My life!
You know that girl?
The burrito girl?
I've always stayed
out of your business,
haven't I?
Because I was hoping
that maybe one day
you would learn
from your mistakes.
You would grow up,
you would mature a bit!
Is my back all right?
(GROANS)
Oh, my God! My back!
You're 26,
and what have you got?
You got, what?
Sixty-five dollars
to your name?
I got tazed.
A car that doesn't start.
You're living on my couch!
Those things work!
Man, look at yourself.
Oh, my God.
As from now,
as from right this second,
there is a new
dynamic at play.
And this dynamic
is the following.
From here on, until
I state otherwise, there
will be no more debate,
no more discussion,
no more compromise!
It's me speaking,
you listening.
Me saying, you doing.
Do you understand that?
It's time for
a new course of action.
A new direction.
A game change.
You are joining
me in the Navy.
ANNOUNCER: Live, local,
this is Hawaii News Now.
Thousands of sailors
on dozens of ships
are coming to
Hawaii for RIMPAC.
NEWSCASTER 1: RIMPAC
is the world's largest
multinational
maritime exercise.
NEWSCASTER 2:
RIMPAC is a military
ballet of 14 navies...
NEWSCASTER 3:
20, 000 Navy personnel.
Cooperation and collaboration
amongst the countries
is the goal.
NEWSCASTER 3:
Relationship-building
is the key.
NEWSCASTER 4: Not all
the action is taking place
out on the water.
There will also be
sporting events
here on land.
Forget World Cup,
this is the RIMPAC Cup final.
ANNOUNCER 1:
It's another beautiful day
here in Hawaii, as usual.
ANNOUNCER 2:
Indeed it is, but a storm
is brewing on the field
as the scrappy U.S.A. team
is butting heads with Japan.
The score is 2-nil, Japan.
The U.S. has been
trailing all day.
Team leader Alex Hopper
has got to do something
to rally the troops here.
Turn it up!
ANNOUNCER 1:
Big save! Great save!
ANNOUNCER 2: Big save!
Stone Hopper, he's answered
every test today.
What's wrong with you,
drama queen?
Get up, princess, come on!
ANNOUNCER 1:
U.S.A.'s Ordy squares the ball
over to number 6, Alan.
ANNOUNCER 2:
Clever backheel
into space...
ANNOUNCER 1:
Hopper... Goal!
(YELLING)
A missile,
past Iwashiro.
The U.S. is finally
on the board, showing
some signs of life
with the score, 2-1, Japan.
ANNOUNCER 2: We are
now into stoppage time.
Can the U.S. tie it up?
Time! Time! Time!
One minute left.
Alex, it's coming your way!
ANNOUNCER 1:
Stone Hopper has
placed it perfectly.
It takes a fortuitous bounce.
Hopper is underneath it
and on-side.
(BOTH GRUNT)
Hey, ref!
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
ANNOUNCER 1: A penalty kick
has been awarded
to the United States.
Nagata made
contact with Hopper
inside the box.
ANNOUNCER 2: And by
"contact," you mean Nagata
kicked him in the face.
STONE: You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
ANNOUNCER 1: Stone Hopper
has come up the field.
I'm fine.
I don't need your help.
Bronson is going
to take it.
Bronson!
What do you mean, "Bronson"?
No, negative.
I'm fine.
Bronson,
you're gonna take this.
Bronson, don't move.
Bronson, come here.
Bronson,
you move one more step,
you're dead!
Do you want to die today?
Do you want to die?
Good choice.
He is definitely concussed.
You just threatened
one of my sailors.
ANNOUNCER 1: Looks like
it's going to be his
little brother, Alex Hopper.
ANNOUNCER 2:
If I was Stone, I would have
picked another shooter.
I'm skeptical that
Hopper is 100 percent.
Engage, engage.
Impose will, impose will.
There are two kinds
of idiots, Hopper.
One looks where he kicks,
the other looks
where he doesn't kick.
Which idiot are you?
I'm the idiot
that's going to kick it
through your keeper's face.
Get ready for overtime.
ANNOUNCER 2:
All eyes on Hopper.
He could send this
into overtime.
(BLOWING WHISTLE)
ANNOUNCER 1:
And here we go.
If Hopper scores,
the U.S. will go
into overtime.
SPECTATORS: Oh!
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
ANNOUNCER 1: Hopper sails one
miles over the crossbar,
nowhere near the goal.
Typical.
ANNOUNCER 2:
What a heartbreak
for the U.S.
(ALL CHEERING)
ANNOUNCER 1: It was a very
poor attempt by the obviously
injured Alex Hopper.
He refused to
come out of the game
and his stubbornness
cost the United States.
Congratulations to Japan,
our 2012 RIMPAC Cup winners.
The final, as we sign off,
Japan, 2.
The United States, 1.
Are you ready for this?
Born.
Are you sure?
Never been more sure
of anything in my life.
What are you going to say?
I'm going to walk up
to him, man to man,
and look him
straight in the eyes.
With what words?
My words.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
"Sir...
"Your daughter
is the best thing
that has ever happened to me.
"She's smart, kind,
beautiful, funny,
"and I'm madly
in love with her.
"It would be an honor
to have your permission
to marry her."
I love you.
I love you, too.
First off, I'd like to
welcome you all to the RIMPAC
International Naval War Games.
And I'd like to
welcome you on board
the greatest fighting ship
in American naval history.
The "Mighty Mo,"
the U.S.S. Missouri.
(CELTIC PUNK MUSIC PLAYING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
SHANE: And fought
in World War II...
Shit!
Hopper, your cover.
I'm keeping you
on your toes.
Hopper, let's go, come on.
Hopper!
HOPPER: This way.
No, no, no.
GUARD: That way, sir.
HOPPER: Yes, yes,
I knew that.
We knew that.
You look good.
The U.S.S. Missouri
was the final battleship
to be completed by
the United States
before being
de-commissioned
and replaced
with a more modern
fleet of vessels,
like destroyers.
What's the difference between
a battleship and a destroyer?
Battleships are great ships.
But they are kind
of like dinosaurs.
They're designed to take hits,
like a floating punching bag.
But then there's destroyers,
which are just awesome.
They're designed
to dish it out
like the Terminator.
Are you a Captain?
No, he's not a Captain
because he's always late.
Come on.
I fight the ship.
Which is even better.
(APPLAUSE)
Listen, get it done.
Get it done.
Babe, it's a formality.
Okay, go.
I'm all over it.
We have with us today,
veterans from the Missouri
who have served on her,
some going back
to World War II.
Examples of the finest
men to have ever
served in any navy.
Lieutenant Hopper,
what an honor.
Thank you for joining us.
Good to be here.
And now,
as we prepare to embark
on this
outstanding exercise...
I'm nervous.
Shades off.
I would like
the Commanding Officers
to come to the stage.
Captain Nagata, Japan.
(GREETS IN JAPANESE)
Captain Lou, Malaysia.
(GREETING IN MALAY)
It's so close to
the way we say it.
He hates me.
He doesn't hate you.
Shut up. Shut up.
SHANE: Captain Jacks,
Australia.
G'day.
Shut up.
G'day!
G'day.
A special acknowledgment
to Commander Stone Hopper,
United States Navy.
Go, that's your call.
Knock 'em out.
Who, along with
his outstanding
crew and ship,
had the highest
overall rating last year.
Shades off, Hopper.
Commander.
Thank you, Admiral.
Welcome, everybody.
It's really great to
see you all here today.
Especially you, gentlemen.
It's a true honor.
Me and my crew,
we're going to have to
be on our toes this year
because your
ships look outstanding
and your men look ready.
So, good luck out there.
Be safe and keep charging.
He loves his daughter,
she loves you.
He's going to respect that.
Hey, Mike.
Admiral.
You remember Sam?
It's an obsolete tradition,
this asking for permission.
Tell me where this came from.
Stop.
Sam's a physical
therapist now.
Stop worrying about this
and walk up and do
what you got to do.
Hello, Hopper.
Why are you here?
This is going
to be sweet.
I was within the rules.
Really?
Were you in the rules
when you kicked
me in the face?
Isn't there something
more important you should
be doing right now?
He hates the man.
That seems a bit juvenile,
wouldn't you say?
Go mess with him
and see what happens.
Why?
CORA: Do it.
Would it be funny
if I punched you
in the face?
Would that be funny?
Stop it.
Chicken.
Kentucky Fried Chicken.
Yeah, I love it.
A two-piece meal.
You look like
Colonel Sanders,
actually.
He was a handsome man.
Good job out there, Dad.
What do you want?
Hopper needs five
minutes of your time.
(SIGHS)
That's enough.
What do you mean?
Don't you have something
more important you should
be doing right now?
Three minutes, tops.
Thank you. I love you.
Thank you, Daddy.
Love you, too.
He's going to
smash my face in.
He's not going to
smash your face in.
Oh, my God.
Sir, it would be an honor.
Sir. Sir. Sir.
Give me your permission.
It would be an honor
to have your permission.
Sir, give me your permission.
What's your deal?
It would be a thankful honor
to have your permission
to honor your hand.
What?
Oh, my God.
Sir,
may I please
marry your daughter?
She's everything I have,
and I love her.
Talking to yourself,
Mr. Hopper?
Yeah, I was.
I was actually talking
about you, Nagata.
Mmm-hmm.
(WHISTLING)
(CRASHING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
HOPPER: That's for
kicking me in the face.
Eat it! Take it!
Let go! Let go.
What the...
(HOPPER YELLS)
Sir, it was a fluke accident.
The bathroom floor was wet.
I began to fall.
Captain Nagata kindly
reached out to help.
YUGI: Our heads go bang.
We fall back.
Bang, again.
Just like the great
Jerry Lewis.
Jerry Lewis?
Did he just say
"Jerry Lewis"?
Yes, sir.
BROWLEY: Are you kidding me?
The Bellboy and original
The Nutty Professor.
Very good movies.
He is a great
humanitarian, sir.
You both think this
is a joke and you are
very much mistaken.
This will not happen again.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, sir.
Gentlemen, give me a minute
with Mr. Hopper, here.
What is wrong with you?
You've got skills,
but I have never ever seen
a man waste them like you.
"Keep the ship out of
the surf and spray..."
"...or you will
plunge to destruction."
Homer, sir.
The fact that you know that
infuriates me beyond words.
What my daughter sees in you
is a great mystery to me.
You are a very
smart individual
with very weak
character, leadership and
decision-making skills.
Do you have anything
to say to me? Anything?
Negative, sir.
Enjoy these naval
exercises, Hopper.
They are likely
to be your last.
Dismissed.
WALTER: Is there anything
I can do to help?
Negative.
If you want to
talk about anything...
I don't.
If you change your mind...
I won't.
Roger that.
Contact DESRON ONE.
Commence anti-submarine
warfare exercises.
Commence air operations.
(SAILORS SHOUTING)
Good afternoon, Sampson.
Welcome to Day One of
the RIMPAC naval war games.
We are here to sharpen
our skills as a team.
HOPPER: As your
weapons officer,
let me remind you
that this is a combat vessel
and we will excel
in our command and control.
STONE: I want everyone
to stay frosty.
We're going to be
close-maneuvering
with 13 nations out here.
We are here to
crush every other ship.
I'm excited to
see what we learn.
We are not here in
this weapons room
to learn.
Be safe out there,
look out for each other
and keep charging.
If we return to Pearl
without having
outperformed every other
ship on that ocean,
I will personally...
Yo, Saunders,
we've ended up
in a department
run by some kind of
Donald Trump/Mike
Tyson mutant combo.
What was that,
Petty Officer Raikes?
CORA: Nothing, sir.
I swear you said,
"Donald Trump."
Want to clarify?
I think I heard
a "Mike Tyson,"
as well.
If you did, it was only
in reference to the fact
that you both project
great physical intensity, sir.
That's flattering.
Hopper! There's a helo
headed for the Sampson.
Make sure your
ass is on it.
Why?
I don't know why!
Just make sure
you're on it!
Copy, sir.
Damn.
PILOT: Scorpion one four,
clear our deck.
En route with parts and techs.
OFFICER: Confirm
Lieutenant Hopper en route.
STONE: I just got off
the phone with the JAG.
And?
They are probably going to
kick you out of the Navy.
When?
The day we get back.
From RIMPAC?
Yeah.
You have got to
make some calls.
There has got to be...
Who do I call to
teach you humility?
I am sorry,
I don't have that number.
I just don't get it, man.
You have got so
much potential.
I'm sorry you have
to deal with this.
And I am sorry
I let you down.
MAN: Stand up nice and tall.
I want you to focus
on that green marker,
right in the middle
of your back.
MICK: What do you think
I'm paying attention to?
MAN: Keep your
feet together.
My feet can't
get any closer.
Stand up tall.
All right.
I had enough of this.
Keep going.
Just a little bit more.
Turn the damned thing off!
Come on.
We're just about there.
Turn it off now!
I'm your new
physical therapist.
I am sensing
a lot of anger.
Very perceptive of you.
Is there anything
besides anger
in there, Mick?
Not much.
Your last therapist
says that you lost
the will to fight.
Is that accurate?
I lost my fight
when I lost my legs.
Do you realize you're still
the same man that won
the Golden Gloves at 22?
A Bronze Star
in Afghanistan?
The same man.
I am half a man.
And half a man ain't
enough to be a soldier.
That's all I have ever known.
All right. Let's go.
We are going
to take a walk.
No, we are not.
Legs on.
SAM: You're doing pretty good
for a guy who doesn't
want to be hiking.
My dog, Mustard,
could climb this mountain.
Great, you and Mustard
can go and make some
memories on Mauna Kea.
Sounds like fun.
Mustard's dead.
Mustard got hit
by a dump truck.
I'm sorry.
I'm over it.
Hey. I thought
you would be
out of range by now.
HOPPER: I have around
five minutes of left time.
SAM: How is it?
It's fine.
I'm sorry. I messed up.
And I'm going to
talk to your father
as soon as I get back.
Stop messing things up, okay?
Copy that. I love you.
I love you.
NOGRADY: What is it, Parker?
Take a look at this.
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Nice one.
It's a joke, right?
I don't think so.
(ALARM BEEPING)
My God.
(HUMMING)
(THE BLUE DANUBE
PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
Cal.
(CONTINUES HUMMING)
Cal!
Huh?
Got some weird activity
on all the radar screens.
Weird?
Yeah, man. Really weird.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, uh, Dr. Nogrady is
on the phone for you, too.
That is weird.
Seriously, Dr. Nogrady?
Lead with that next time.
Okay, Danny?
You got to start
prioritizing your information.
If you have to
tell me "1, 2, 3,"
you don't start with "M."
You know what I mean?
I mean, I'm not saying
that you are a boob,
but this is
boob-ish behavior.
Hi, Dr. Nogrady.
Are you seeing
what I am seeing?
The incoming tracks.
Correct.
I've got five
distinct objects...
Five distinct objects
that are moving in formation.
They are locked
in on my signal.
They are headed
straight for me.
Correct.
Maybe we should call NASA.
NASA have called us.
They're on
the phone right now.
Good morning,
Mr. Zapata.
NASA?
We are tracking something
splintering off
of the main group.
That's not splitting off.
That thing is breaking apart.
Has anyone called the Chinese?
Because this is no meteor.
Yes, we have checked.
It's not the Russians,
it's not the Chinese.
Maybe we should
call the Air Force,
because they might want
to fuel up their jets.
NOGRADY: The Air Force
is online.
It appears the event
is headed your way.
Prepare yourself.
Roger that.
How would you suggest
that I prepare myself, sir?
Brace.
(SCREAMS)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
MAN 1: Let's all be seated.
I am hoping somebody here
can explain this to me.
CHAIRMAN: Mr. Secretary,
four of the five objects
landed in the Pacific Ocean.
The fifth one
appeared to have
broken apart
making significant
contact with Hong Kong,
but other places
were also affected.
Scotland, Germany,
France, even Iowa.
So, what is it?
Sir, at this point
we are working on
a couple of theories.
And you are who, sir?
I am with NASA.
What is NASA present
in this room for?
NASA DIRECTOR: We are looking
at the very real possibility
that this is legitimate
extraterrestrial contact.
It appears that it originated
from the Gliese solar system.
Home of Planet G.
You are saying that
we sent out a signal
and we got back
an alien response?
WATCH OFFICER: Sir, we just
got word from Pearl.
They believe
whatever made impact
with Hong Kong,
has also made impact
with the Pacific Ocean.
Where in the Pacific?
Approximately
150 miles south of
where we are right now, sir.
It should be right there,
but we are not
seeing anything.
Get me the Sampson.
Yes, sir.
Base course, 2-2-0. Speed, 25.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
BRIDGE OFFICER:
Captain on the bridge!
As casualty reports come in,
it's still unclear
exactly what it was
that hit Hong Kong.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
It isn't anything
from this planet.
How do we know that?
Because the Chinese
have sampled it.
It's made of a material
that does not exist
in the periodic table.
It's literally
not of this Earth.
The only element
they've been able to
identify is lawrencium.
Lawrencium?
You got to stop tapping.
You're tapping.
You're the loud one.
NOGRADY: Looking at
the grid patterns,
it's something in
the neighborhood
of solar paneling
or communications paneling.
It may be some kind of
a communication unit.
Communications?
Who is communicating what?
To who?
(JIMMY WHISTLING)
JIMMY: What the heck is that?
Bridge, starboard lookout.
I've got an unknown
surface contact.
Bearing is 2-3-2 true,
approximately 8,000 yards.
Sir?
STONE: Yeah.
You may want to come
take a look at this.
I am looking at it,
Mr. Strodell.
On the radar, sir.
Something very peculiar.
STONE: That's the
John Paul Jones, right?
Yes, sir.
The Myoko?
Yes, sir, it is.
So, why don't I see...
See that?
Combat, Captain. I have
a visual on the track bearing
2-3-7 on the horizon.
What do you hold
in that bearing?
Bridge, TAO.
I've got nothing at 2-3-7.
I'm looking right at it,
Mr. Hopper.
Find me something.
Scope, 2-3-7,
what do you got?
Stand by.
That's negative, sir.
Scope's clear, I got nothing.
Taylor, did you break
this son-of-a-bitch?
No, I didn't do
anything to it, sir.
You know I will throw
your ass off this ship.
I know you will, sir.
Got it, sir.
On my camera.
What is it?
I don't know.
Is this some
kind of exercise?
Probably.
Unknown vessel in the
vicinity of 1 -5 degrees,
3-7 minutes north,
and 1-5-9 degrees,
3-3 minutes west.
Request you
establish communications
with my vessel
on VHF channel 16,
and identify yourself, over.
John Paul Jones,
this is Sampson,
Charlie Oscar.
John Paul Jones,
I would like you
to send a team over
and take a closer look.
No problem.
We will get a team in
the water right away.
Roger.
I'll tell you what, boys,
this is a head-stumper.
(SINGING INDISTINCTLY)
WALTER: What is it?
Lost cargo? Chinese?
I don't know.
Yacht? Satellite?
Beast, I didn't know
five seconds ago,
and I don't know now.
This is the U.S. Navy warship
John Paul Jones.
I'm attempting to
communicate with you.
Prepare to be boarded.
You ever seen
anything like this?
No.
It's weird, man.
(HOLLOW BANGING)
LT! I don't think
that's a good idea.
Got it, chief.
Real bad idea, Lieutenant.
(YELLS)
Oh, shit.
Move it, Raikes!
WALTER: LT!
Lieutenant, get up!
Lieutenant!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Sir!
Get me the Sampson.
WATCH OFFICER: Alpha Bravo.
Sampson, this is Alpha Bravo.
Sir, we're unable to
contact the Sampson.
Reagan control, this is
Rough Rider 4-0-4.
I'm encountering
some severe...
Rough Rider 4-0-4, come in.
Do you copy?
Put the force at
weapons posture one.
Warning red, weapons tight.
I want everything loaded.
OFFICER: Bridge,
what's happened?
My radar's totally down, sir.
EXECUTIVE OFFICER: We've lost
contact with base. All comms
are offline.
It's the North Koreans,
I'm telling you.
Hey, Lieutenant, you good?
Come on, you with me?
Come on. Damn it!
Come on! Squared away?
I'm squared away.
Whatever that thing is,
it killed the battery.
Come on, Beast.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
What is that?
That's not good.
What the hell is that?
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Do you think that
this could be some
super-secret Navy
surprise exercise?
Because if so,
they have gone
way too far.
Let's give them
a warning, Helmsman.
Aye, aye, sir.
(FOGHORN BLOWING)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
What the hell is this?
I didn't sign up
for this bullshit!
Yeah, no shit, dude.
Klyvich is offline.
Should be back
in two minutes.
Copy that.
Signal the John Paul Jones.
Fire a warning shot.
One round, ten mil,
left offset.
Place Mount 51 in remote,
batteries released.
WEAPONS OFFICER:
Mount 51 has been designated.
Who are we shooting at?
I do not know.
CORA: Let's move it, Beast.
WALTER: She's dead
in the water.
Ord, get your ass
to the lee helm.
Aye, sir.
MULLENARO: Fire!
Incoming, headed for
the John Paul Jones.
Unknown, inbound
at the horizon.
Vampire, vampire, vampire.
Killing with CIWS.
What kind of
chuckwagon...
Were there men out
on that bridge wing?
Yes, sir, there were.
I got it! Firing it up!
HOPPER: Get in there!
Sir!
Light it up!
(SCREAMING)
MAN: What the hell
is Hopper doing?
All engines, ahead flank.
All engines ahead.
Aye, sir!
Sir,
CIC reports both Spy and Fire
control radar cannot lock on.
Fire!
CIC, fire!
Incoming on the right!
JOOD: Incoming, incoming!
We're hit!
(ALL SCREAMING)
HELMSMAN: Sir, we have
a hull breach.
(ALL CLAMORING)
Help me!
Helmsman,
get back on the helm!
Aye, sir.
Rapid, continued fire!
No!
(EXCLAIMS IN JAPANESE)
Get me to the
John Paul Jones.
Now!
RADIO OPERATOR: Bridge reports
no survivors in the water.
Sampson, all hands lost.
Targets are holding
defensive formation.
Where's the captain?
Where is he?
What happened?
OFFICER: Captain
and XO are dead.
What?
They're dead!
CO and XO are dead.
Who's in charge?
Who's next full senior?
You are.
It's your ship, sir.
You're senior officer, sir.
Sir, if you would
please just give me
an order.
I don't know
what to do, sir.
We're going in.
Full attack.
That's an order.
Attack, sir? Really?
You wanted an order,
that's the order. Let's go.
Let's go!
You heard him.
HELMSMAN: Aye, aye, sir!
Ready all guns.
Fire control is offline.
I need three minutes.
Tell Nagata I'm going in,
with or without him.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Sir, do you really
want to attack this thing?
Yes! Yes, I do.
(SHOUTS IN JAPANESE)
JIMMY: Sir, that's a hit!
The Myoko was hit, sir.
Are the weapons ready?
Sir, they have killed
everything that's fired
on them.
Get the guns online,
and we ram this thing.
They killed my brother
and every man on his ship!
We have no weapons
to attack with, sir.
Then set course to 3-1 -0.
That's a collision course!
Are you clear on that?
WALTER: Sir, there are
sailors in the water.
Get the guns online
and we're going
to ram this thing!
Sir, the Myoko is sinking!
Sir, please!
Set the course to 3-1 -0.
There are sailors
in the water, sir!
Hard starboard.
Hard starboard. Aye, sir!
Get them out of the water.
Yes, sir.
(SIGHS)
GUNNER: What's happening?
Shut up, man.
What the hell is happening?
What the hell are
they doing? Why aren't
they attacking?
GUNNER: Are those
things aliens?
Would you please shut up?
GUNNER: We need help!
We need to get
the carrier over here!
Who's running the ship?
Hopper.
Are you kidding me?
Hopper's running the ship?
This is bullshit.
We're all going to die!
What the hell
are those things?
What is that shit?
BASE OFFICER:
Comms are down up here.
You got anything?
PILOT 1: That's a negative
on all frequencies.
Oh, shit.
HELICOPTER GUNNER:
Abandon 9-30!
PILOT 2: Kill the engines!
Strike!
MAN: Hey, Jack!
Dad?
SHANE: Sir,
I can't explain this.
We've lost communication
with everyone
on the other side
of the barrier.
We can't get in and
they can't get out.
CHAIRMAN: The field,
whatever it is, extends about
300,000 feet in altitude
and has a depth of
about two nautical miles.
COMMANDANT: We are
in contact with Admiral
Shane of Pacific Fleet.
Right now, our navy
is effectively trapped
outside the area.
So we have nobody in there?
Sir, we have three
guided missile destroyers
still unaccounted for.
So, it's conceivable
we do have somebody inside.
Who?
(SAILORS CLAMORING)
Okay. Thank you!
Captain! Captain!
(SHOUTING IN JAPANESE)
YUGI: Let's go! Let's go!
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
My grandmother could
climb this mountain.
It's a start, Mick.
What was that?
I'm not sure.
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(SIREN CHIRPS)
What the hell
are you guys
doing up here?
I need you off this
mountain, right now.
Wait, what's going on? Why?
The island's under attack.
Attack by who?
I don't know.
People are using
the word "aliens."
Aliens?
We don't know.
Whatever it is,
it took out the marine base
and all roads
leading to this mountain
have been destroyed.
Cell phones, radios, Internet,
everything is shut down.
The Navy's engaged,
just off of the coast.
The Navy?
I need you and your friend
off of this mountain
right now.
Come on, let's go.
Vic, leave your car here.
We'll go block the road.
Where are you going?
Mick! Where are you going?
I ain't never seen an alien.
Have you ever seen an alien?
Mick! Don't leave me alone.
Bra, you saw that?
What the hell was that?
Hey, Vince,
did you see that?
VINCE: It looked like a jet.
Bra, I've never...
Oh, my God! What the hell?
(SCREAMS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Sir, we need you.
We need you now.
I can't.
If you can't...
Who can?
Captain.
HOPPER: Where did we find it?
JIMMY: One of their
transporters must have crashed
on the way to the island.
There was debris everywhere.
Thomas and Potts fished him
right out of the water
with a grappling hook.
I told them
it was a bad idea,
but they kept yanking.
I kept telling them "no,"
and they kept...
Hmm...
(GRUNTS)
Oh...
(ALL EXCLAIM IN SHOCK)
God damn it!
Beast, flashlight.
My dad said they would come.
He said it my whole life.
He said, "We ain't alone."
He said, "One day
we would find them,
"or they would find us."
You know what else he said?
He said...
"I hope I ain't around
when that day comes."
(GASPING)
He's not dead!
Not dead! Not dead!
(GRUNTS)
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
What kind of bad feeling?
Like, "We're going
to need a new planet"
kind of bad feeling.
RADIO OFFICER: Medical
casualty, C-53. Two men down.
They're still on the ship.
Lock down the ship!
Is everyone all right?
OFFICER 1: All good, Chief.
Is everyone accounted for?
OFFICER 2: (ON RADIO)
Just heard something
on Level Four.
Raikes, up.
(SCREAMS)
Hey! Move, move!
HOPPER: What do you see?
Did you see it?
No, sir.
I got nothing, sir!
Nothing.
How is he?
Not good, sir. Not good.
You two, get him
to medical, now!
Raikes, you're with me.
Let's go!
(FAINT HYDRAULIC HISSING)
(LOUD BANG)
Get out of here!
No!
(YELLS)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
Yo! Hey!
(GROANING)
HOPPER: Raikes...
Get your ass to CIC.
Now!
Come on.
(GRUNTING)
Raikes, you better be there.
Come on, come on, come on.
Mahalo, mother...
We got to get
off this mountain.
The cop left the keys
on his belt.
You've got to go
down and get them.
You can do it.
(SNORTS)
(HYDRAULIC HISSING)
(WHIMPERING)
Now.
(STATIC CRACKLING)
This is an emergency call.
Can anyone hear me?
Radio check.
Can anyone hear me? Over.
Hey, wait up!
Don't leave! Don't leave!
Stop right there!
Don't shoot!
Who are you?
I'm Cal Zapata.
We sent out a beacon.
Oh, shit, is he a cyborg?
Are you guys with them?
If he's human,
could you have him
put the gun down?
SAM: Mick,
put your gun down.
I told them that something
like this could happen.
I said, it's going
to be like Columbus
and the Indians,
or the Conquistadors
and the Incans.
They just thought,
"No, they will be sweet."
They killed my grad student.
(GASPING)
Okay, calm down.
I can't.
Slow. Sit down.
I can't breathe.
SAM: Slow breaths,
slow breaths.
You're freaking
him out, Mick.
I doubt it takes
much to freak him out.
We need the Marines.
We need the Army.
We need all of them.
NOGRADY: It is the strong
belief of the Chinese
that what crashed
into Hong Kong
was some sort of
communications ship.
You're saying that
a flying telephone cratered
and took out 25,000 people?
What I'm saying is that
our visitors seem
extraordinarily concerned
with establishing a line
of communication home.
If they have lost
their communication ship,
how could they do that?
The same way we did.
Our communications
station in Hawaii
has the ability
to send a message
to deep space via
the Landsat 7 satellite.
I believe it's for that asset
they have domed the islands.
We're looking at
an extinction-level event.
The most critical part
of any military operation.
Establish communications,
reinforcements,
follow-on forces.
You're saying E.T.
wants to phone home?
That would be incredibly,
incredibly bad.
So far, only five ships
have made contact.
If five ships can do this,
what do you think 50 can do,
or 500 or 5,000 or 500,000?
JIMMY: Sir, if I could
just have a minute.
If you'll just
give me one second...
Why am I staring
at a lizard?
Because this is
my pet lizard, sir.
Penelope the Third.
And?
And they have
the exact same eyes.
You have 15 seconds. Go.
Okay, sir,
I put the helmet on,
and the helmet is, basically,
extreme sunglasses.
And it's some hydration
and some oxygen saturation,
and a bunch of other stuff
I don't understand.
But we took Penelope
to the beach one time,
which was a terrible idea.
She went absolutely crazy
because she can't
handle the sunlight.
You see? I don't think
that they can handle
the sunlight either.
You try anything else on?
Negative, sir.
Just the helmet.
Scientists have confirmed
there was a UFO landing
in the Pacific Ocean,
off the coast of Hawaii.
Today I want to update
the American people
on what we know about
the situation in Hawaii.
First, we are bringing all
available resources to bear.
(ALARM WAILING)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
NEWSCASTER: The news has
sparked global unrest
as populations panic,
unleashing an unprecedented
wave of chaos
across the world.
Many governments have
declared martial law.
MAN: Just scramble
the jets, Admiral.
We need to get in there!
I'm far from more aware
than you of the need
to get inside there.
But wasting lives
will not help.
You want me to
send up another plane?
I'll do it the second
you come up here
and put your ass in
the co-pilot's seat, sir!
Are they transmitting?
They could be,
but it wouldn't
do them any good.
There's no satellite
to receive the transmission.
We beam to Landsat 7.
What's Landsat 7?
It's our deep-space satellite.
It only orbits into range
once every 24 hours.
When is the satellite
in position?
8:43 a.m.
We've got about five hours.
And then they will
use it to slingshot
their transmission.
Slingshot where?
I don't know.
Wherever it is they're from.
HOPPER: Pearl Harbor here,
we're approximately here,
and they, whatever they are,
are somewhere in the middle.
We're trapped out here.
What we know right now
is we can't target them
unless we have
a plain line of sight.
Without radar, we have no
way to track them, correct?
Correct. But I don't think
they can see us, either.
Why?
Because we are still alive.
Okay, so they can't see us
and we can't see them.
And we have no way
to hit them from
a safe distance.
There is a way.
A way?
A way of seeing them,
without seeing them.
You're going to
reference Art of War
right now, aren't you?
What are we supposed
to do, fight the enemy
where they aren't?
Move like water?
Because I've read
that thing six times.
It makes no sense.
That book is Chinese.
It still makes no sense.
My way is much more simple.
We've been doing it to
America for 20 years.
Water displacement.
How do you track
water displacement?
Tsunami buoys.
Tsunami buoys?
You have them
surrounding your islands,
transmitting
displacement data.
We hack into their
transmissions,
form a grid.
You can't track
anything without radar.
I don't need radar.
Just the radio frequencies.
Turn off Aegis radar, please.
JIMMY: Who is this guy?
Chief Moore.
OFFICER: Sir.
Secure SPY.
OFFICER: Securing SPY, sir.
Display NOAA data.
NOAA data?
That's correct.
You heard him.
Display NOAA data.
(CLEARS THROAT)
CORA: What the hell is that?
HOPPER: It's a buoy.
If it gets hit by a wave,
it transmits a signal.
(BEEPING)
Bring up chart plot.
Chart plot. Bring it up.
So we can track
without radar.
We would practice it
as a contingency plan.
You dirty,
cheating, sneaky...
Rough world.
I like it.
Captain.
My chair is your chair, sir.
My brother would
have done the same.
I wish we could
get a hold of Hopper.
Who's Hopper?
He's a tactical
actions officer
on an Arleigh Burke
class destroyer.
It has the resources
that could take this
entire mountain out.
Great, that makes
a lot of sense.
Let's call him.
We can't.
Everything is jammed.
They're using
an electromagnetic field
to block our signals.
It's more like a pulse,
it's not a brick wall.
There are gaps, okay?
From inside the barrier,
we might just be
able to get a call out.
If I could get to
my spectrum analyzer,
then, theoretically,
we could find a frequency
we could broadcast on...
Do you have
a piece of equipment
that can make a call?
Yeah.
Get it.
I can't because
it's down there,
in that nest of aliens.
You're going to go get it.
No.
Yes.
SAM: Yes.
We are looking for patterns
of water displacement.
HOPPER: That buoy
is underwater.
That's a ship.
Get on your gun.
Yes, sir.
Target, Echo-1 -1.
CORA: Roger. Echo 1 -1.
Ready to fire.
When we fire,
they will know where we are.
Fire!
Ordy, anything?
JIMMY: Negative, sir.
It's a miss.
It's heading towards us.
You ready?
I'm sorry,
but there is no possible way
that I'm going down there.
I do not possess
that kind of courage.
Right now,
you're going to
acquire that courage,
or I'm going to
break my steel leg off
into your ass.
You feel me?
I feel you.
Go, now.
Acquiring courage.
What?
Foxtrot, 2-4.
CORA: Foxtrot, 2-4.
Ready to fire.
Fire!
Ordy, anything?
JIMMY: Negative, sir.
It's a stupid,
nincompoop idea.
There's another one.
JIMMY: Incoming, incoming!
Sir, they're coming
from both directions!
Engines, back, full.
Incoming, incoming, incoming!
India 3-7.
India 3-7. Loaded.
Second coordinate,
Romeo, 2-6.
Romeo 2-6.
Sir, we're hot over here.
Missiles good to go.
Let's light them up,
Captain Nagata.
Fire!
Holy shit!
A hit, sir! Hit!
(EXCLAIMING IN JAPANESE)
(ALL CHEERING)
MICK: Any station this net,
any station this net,
this is a call for help.
Any warship, police
or military personnel,
please respond, over.
This is U.S.S.
John Paul Jones,
state your identity
and position. Over.
Hopper?
Sam?
Sam, are you okay?
Where are you?
Thank God. I'm okay.
Listen, they're here
at the satellite array
at Saddle Ridge, do you copy?
They're going to
transmit a signal
and establish communication.
You need to
destroy the facility.
We have four hours.
Four hours, I copy.
Hopper.
SAM: Can you hear me?
Babe, you need to
get out of there.
Hopper? Hopper?
No, they're gone.
They're gone.
MICK: We better
get gone, too.
I'm thinking an Arleigh
Burke class destroyer
is about to rain hell
down on this mountaintop.
Are you ready to
kill another one?
Tango 1 -9.
Tango 1 -9. Loaded.
Whiskey 2-5.
CORA: Whiskey 2-5.
Raikes, can you get
a track on their ship?
Negative, sir, it's
moving all over the place.
I can't get a line on it.
This sucker's
really jumping around.
Very intelligent.
What time is sunrise?
CORA: Forty minutes, sir.
Let's take these bastards
somewhere they
don't want to go.
CORA: General quarters,
general quarters.
All hands, man
your battle stations.
I need to know when
we round this point
if we can hold her tight.
Right around
Diamond Head, here.
WALTER: There's
a brutal current there.
It will take a miracle
to keep her off the reef.
Ordy, is it possible?
Can you do it?
It's not impossible.
Sir, I can try,
but I don't know what...
Can you do it,
yes or no?
Contact is seven miles out,
and closing fast.
Yes, sir, I can do it.
Check safe, check clear.
Get some.
Captain Nagata,
how good is your aim?
Excellent.
OFFICER: All right,
let's start this turn!
JOOD: Aye, sir!
Left, hard rudder!
Left, hard rudder, sir!
How are we looking?
It's all reef.
Ordy, you are way
too close! Come left!
Easy...
We're about to kiss
these rocks, Ordy!
Ordy!
HOPPER: Where did you
learn to shoot?
I'm not sure how
you say it in English.
Natsu campu.
Summer campu.
How about now?
GUNNER: Still a little tight.
I can see fish, Ordy.
Come on, man.
CORA: Contact,
two miles out.
Contact ETA, 21 seconds.
Summer campu.
CORA: Contact,
700 yards out.
Summer camp.
Champion, when I was 12.
Are you kidding me?
Here we go.
On my mark.
Three.
Two.
One.
Light them up.
Boom.
(ALL CHEERING)
OFFICER: (ON RADIO)
Three miles until Saddle Ridge
is within range.
Status of weps.
JOOD: Sir, they're
bringing up all the rounds
from the lower mag right now.
JIMMY: Sir.
Clear the bridge.
Clear the bridge!
Shit!
(GRUNTING)
Ordy, get up! Let's go!
Go, go, go!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
SAILOR 1: We've got
two down, sir!
Get up.
SAILOR 2: Go, go, go!
Get in the water! Go!
It's going down!
Come on.
(ALL CLAMORING)
(GASPS)
Raikes!
Right here!
You're almost there, come on!
Let's go,
we have to jump!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
SAM: That's the
John Paul Jones.
That's Hopper.
Relax, Sam.
I'm seeing a lot of
lifeboats in the water.
You say that satellite
will be in position
in three hours?
Yeah, that's correct.
So if they miss it,
they have to wait.
My uplink never misses.
It's not going to miss.
How are your driving skills?
What does that mean?
How are my driving skills?
They're horrible.
Not your driving.
Sam, how are your
driving skills?
Good.
Let's see if we can't buy
the world another day.
Who talks like that?
MICK: Just get
in the vehicle.
Let's go.
I'm not getting in.
This is your show, now.
I don't have a death wish,
thank you very much.
Goodbye, everyone.
Stop! Stop.
This is my property.
It doesn't end like this.
What do you want
us to do, Hopper?
We have no ships left.
We have one.
We have got a battleship.
Are you crazy?
That's a museum.
Not today.
This ship is 70 years old.
It's totally outdated.
The firing systems
are all analog.
The engines
haven't been started
in a decade.
Which would be fine,
but they are steam,
which I have no idea
how to fire up.
And even if I had
a user's manual
and six weeks to
go through it all,
we still don't have
enough crew to fire it up.
I don't know what
you're thinking, sir.
Is everyone all right?
Yes, sir. We're okay.
You men have given so much
to your country,
and no one has the right
to ask any more of you,
but I'm asking.
What do you need, son?
I need to borrow your boat.
Son.
Sir.
What the hell?
Are you going to stand there,
staring at me?
Get your goddamn eye
on that spotter!
Eye on spotter, sir.
Been working
on a destroyer,
haven't you?
Yes, sir.
Are you ready to play
with the big boys?
Oh, yes, sir.
Come on.
We need the help.
Awesome!
Best cover your ears.
(STEAM HISSING)
(POWERING UP)
Purrs like a kitten.
Bridge, main control.
I got eight boilers hot.
Ready to rock and roll, sir.
How are we looking on fuel?
600 long tons, sir.
Just enough for
a maintenance run.
Ordnance?
We scraped together
what we could, sir.
But it's not much.
All right,
let's get her to sea.
We have got work to do.
Roger that.
Engines ahead, flank.
All engines ahead, flank.
Aye, sir.
You good?
VETERAN: Good, sir.
Good, sir.
Good.
Status of turret one?
Center line, barrel, armed.
GUNNER: Stop!
WALTER: Clear!
GUNNER: Loaded.
VETERAN: Status of turret two?
Starboard side, armed.
VETERAN: Status
of turret three?
Port barrel.
Ready to rock and roll.
Port side, armed!
Sir, are we really
firing on Oahu?
Sure looks that way.
Holy shit!
CORA: Saddle Ridge
will be in weapons range
in five minutes.
Oh, brother,
somebody is going
to kiss the donkey.
Hopper!
I didn't think
that one moved.
Me neither.
My God.
Are you kidding me?
Art of War.
HOPPER: Fire control,
weapons status?
Aimed at target.
Train all three
turrets to 2-1 -0.
CORA: But, sir,
that's the wrong direction!
I'm well aware
of that, Raikes.
What the hell is he doing?
He's losing his mind,
all over again.
Hard left rudder.
Hard left rudder. Aye, sir.
Drop port anchor.
What?
Drop it now!
We are going to die.
You are going to die.
I am going to die.
We are all going to die.
Just not today.
Let's drop some
lead on those mother...
Fire!
Reload! Reload!
Firing mechanism reset!
Secure the hatch.
Port side ready!
Release the anchor.
Incoming! Incoming!
(SCREAMING)
You all right?
They ain't going to
sink this battleship,
no way.
Hit it!
Everything you've got!
Whoo!
(SNARLS)
I want every available plane
on this ship in the air, now!
I can't believe
that worked!
Yeah, Art of War.
Fight the enemy
where they aren't.
After all these years,
that finally just clicked.
But that's not
what it means.
Really?
Not even close.
MICK: Keep going!
Oh, shit!
Mick, my leg is stuck.
Mick!
HOPPER: Status of weapons?
VETERAN: Turret three is down.
We got one round
of high-explosive
back-aft in turret three.
Tell them to have it
ready when we get there.
I got this.
Beast, update.
I need that round.
We need to bring
it to turret two.
Sir?
Turret two is 500 feet away.
This round is over
a thousand pounds!
How do you expect
us to get it there?
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
Raikes! Get to the gun plot,
finger on the trigger.
Yes, sir.
Come on, easy. Easy.
GUNNER: Gentle, boys.
Gentle, gentle.
Get out of here!
We got to go.
Calm down, okay?
I'm going to
frigging save you.
Closed, number one is armed.
Coordinates?
Train, 3-3-0.
Elevation?
2-2-0.
There! Go!
Let's go!
She's armed.
You better not be up there.
Let's go! Come on!
Hopper!
We only have one
round left, right?
Yeah.
It was an honor
serving with you,
Captain.
The honor was mine.
Fire.
Locked on target.
(ALL CHEERING)
SHANE: We take great
pride in honoring
the many men and women
who demonstrated
exceptional gallantry
in the face of
overwhelming enemy force.
Valor and courage
were exhibited by so many
that I cannot honor them all.
It is my great
privilege to recognize
those few whose actions
deserve special note.
Lieutenant Colonel,
United States Army,
retired, Mick Canales.
(CROWD CHEERING)
The President of
the United States
takes great pleasure
in presenting the Navy Cross
to Commander Stone Hopper
for extraordinary heroism.
Receiving this award,
on behalf of his brother,
Lieutenant
Commander Alex Hopper.
Stand fast, Mr. Hopper.
It is my great pleasure
to present you
with a Silver Star
for your exceptional
heroism and gallantry
in combat operations.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
And I look forward
to seeing you at sea
on a ship of your
own command, soon.
Thank you.
(ALL WHOOPING)
(INDISTINCT)
Ordy, stop talking
for a second.
Come on, take
the picture, Beast.
Say "Navy."
Navy!
(LAUGHS)
Mildly impressive, Hopper.
You ready to get your ass
off that big gray monster,
get out to Coronado
and get your hands dirty
with the big boys?
Yes, sir.
You think you've
got what it takes?
I hope so, sir.
Call me, Hopper.
It just might be too
much sleep, though, sir.
A little too much
sleep for you?
Yes, sir.
We will have to
see about that.
Come on, Hopper,
cozy up to Nagata.
You look so cute.
You guys make a great couple.
Are we dating now?
You look dapper.
"Navy." Say, "Navy."
Yeah, I don't know.
Oh!
Bad timing.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
How are you?
Good, how are you?
I love you.
I'm a pretty lucky guy,
you know that?
Which is why I think
it's a perfect time
for you to talk to my dad.
Where is he?
I wish he was
standing right here.
That's perfect,
because look!
Your wish came true,
honey. Go get him.
Thumbs up, that helps.
(SIGHS)
Sir.
(CLEARS THROAT)
What is it?
I want you to know
that I am in love with Sam.
And I am asking
your permission
to marry your daughter.
No.
Thank you, sir.
I mean, it's...
What?
No.
Sir...
I saved the world.
Saving the world is
one thing, Hopper.
My daughter is quite another.
But...
No means no, Hopper.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm late for lunch.
I think I will have
a chicken burrito.
Chicken...
Sir.
Come along, Hopper.
We will discuss the terms
of your surrender over a meal.
Yes, sir.
She told you about that?
You got nothing on Jay-Z.
I mean,
even I couldn't
get Beyoncé.
I couldn't get
Beyoncé either.
No way.
Whoa.
What the...
THOM: What is that?
Don't get too close to it.
Whoa, guys! Look at this!
ANGUS: Don't go too close!
THOM: Don't run to it.
Do you think that
looks like a door?
ANGUS: A door?
Hello?
Anyone home?
ANGUS: That's not
going to help, is it?
This really helps.
(HORN HONKING)
THOM: Do you know
what that is?
RONNIE: We think there's
something inside of it.
THOM: Are going
to open it, Jimmy?
If Jimmy says
he's getting in,
he's getting in!
Come on, Jimmy!
Whoo!
Jimmy!
That's it. Come to daddy.
(MUFFLED CHEERS)
ANGUS: Jimmy! Oh, my God!
Yes!
(PANTING)
(ALL SCREAMING)